Anti-Semitism is the hatred of Jews because they are Jews.
Anti-Zionism is an opposition either to the Zionist ideology,
the official ideology of the straight opinion,
or more commonly, it's criticism of specific policies of the Israeli government,
and particularly policies towards the Palestinians, policies of the occupation.
Anti-Semitism is a very ugly thing and should never be justified.
Most of the anti-Zionism, as I have this day,
are the statements that I've come across are reasonable, evidence-based, and legitimate.
But the problem is that Israel and its friends,
and its very powerful friends around the world,
deliberately, deliberately conflict the two.
So as to pretend to claim that any criticism of the state of Israel
and its policies is anti-Semitism.
And the last example of that I've already given at the beginning of my talk,
which is the Secretary General of the United Nations,
who made a very humane statement about the need to ceasefire and protect civilians.
And the Israeli representative immediately accused the sea of anti-Semitism.
So this is a very clear illustration of the strategies of Israel and its friends around the world.